Everyone's a critic.
Heckler is a documentary, comedy film directed by Michael Addis.
HECKLER is a comedic feature documentary exploring the
increasingly critical world we live in.
After starring in a film that was critically bashed, Jamie Kennedy takes on hecklers and critics and ask some interesting
questions of people such as George Lucas, Bill Maher, Mike Ditka, Rob Zombie, Howie Mandel and many more.
This fast moving, hilarious documentary pulls no punches as you see an uncensored look at just how
nasty and mean the fight is between those in the spotlight and those in the dark.
Self, played by Stephen Burrows.
Self, played by Criss Angel.
Self, played by Louie Anderson.
Self, played by Simon Rex.
Self, played by Dave Attell.
Self, played by Maria Bamford.
Heckler is a 2007 documentary film about hecklers.
The film is hosted by actor and comedian Jamie Kennedy, who was inspired to create the movie after feeling hurt by the overwhelmingly poor reception of his
2005 film Son of the Mask, in which reviewers and fans of the original 1994 film attacked Kennedy personally rather than reviewing the film.
Interviewees include comedians Louie Anderson, Kathy Griffin, Bobby Slayton, Patton Oswalt, Joe Rogan, Arsenio Hall, Carrot Top, Maria Bamford and George Wallace; medical doctor Drew Pinsky; writer Christopher Hitchens;
political commentator Dennis Prager; producer Peter Guber; directors Joel Schumacher, George Lucas; film critics Leonard Maltin and Devin Faraci, director and musician Rob Zombie; and singer Jewel Kilcher.
Heckler also includes footage of much-derided filmmaker Uwe Boll's
boxing matches with several of his most vocal critics.
The film explores themes of screenwriter, comedian,
sexism, racist remark, racist comment.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.